good morning good afternoon and good
早上好，下午好
evening
晚间
my name is Peter Humphrey I'm a
我的名字叫彼得·汉弗莱（Peter Humphrey）
principal product marketing manager at
首席产品营销经理
pivotal working on the spring team and
春季团队的关键工作
Cloud Foundry teams I am lucky enough to
Cloud Foundry团队我很幸运
be joined today by one of the newest
今天被最新的之一加入
members of the spring butene mother Oh
春季丁烯妈妈的成员哦
would you introduce yourself and maybe
你会自我介绍吗？
tell us a little bit about who you are
告诉我们你的身份
and how you got here okay Thank You PJ
以及如何到达这里好吧，谢谢PJ
so hi everyone my name is mother Jeff
大家好，我叫杰夫妈妈
happy and I am a developer on the single
很高兴，我是单身的开发人员
team like Peter said I just joined the
像彼得这样的团队说我刚加入
team a few months ago and before that I
几个月前，在此之前，我
was working on Cloud Foundry more
在Cloud Foundry上工作更多
specifically the user authentication and
特别是用户身份验证和
authorization component of Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry的授权组件
also known as the UA a that product so
也称为UA a that product so
you a is a string project it's one of
你是一个字符串项目，它是其中之一
the few spring projects on Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry上的几个春季项目
and I I think I was lucky enough to make
我觉得我很幸运
the switch to a string boot and get to
切换到字符串启动并进入
work on some awesome string boot and
在一些很棒的字符串启动上工作，
cloud foundry integrations as soon as I
我马上就进行了Cloud Foundry集成
joined in fact I think yeah we're
事实上我加入了，是的
excited to have you oh cool so on today
很高兴有你哦，今天如此酷
we're going to talk about spring boots
我们将谈论 spring boot
the new spring point one five release
新的春天点一五发布
and talked a little bit about how that
并谈到了如何
works on total Cloud Foundry and some of
适用于整个Cloud Foundry和一些
the exciting things that so we are doing
我们正在做的令人兴奋的事情
as a joint engineering team but before
作为联合工程团队，但之前
we get into that let's just kind of do a
我们了解到，让我们来做一个
quick little recap of what's been
快速回顾一下发生了什么
happening in some of the latest releases
在某些最新版本中发生
just obligatory safe harbor statement
只是强制性的安全港声明
since we are going to be talking about a
因为我们要谈论的是
little bit of forward facing roadmap
前瞻性路线图的一点点
information you know you'll notice the
您知道的信息会注意到
conspicuous absence of dates and such um
没有明显的日期和这样的数字
so you know just realize that some of
所以你知道，只是意识到
this information is forward facing it
这些信息是正向的
and may change well make it very clear
并可能会很好地改变
when we get into the forward facing
当我们进入前向时
information though it should be pretty
信息虽然应该很漂亮
obvious cool so let's talk a little bit
很酷，让我们谈一点
about start off by talking a little bit
关于通过谈一点开始
about what happened in boot 1/4 in case
关于开机1/4发生的情况
you missed it we're going to focus on
您错过了它，我们将专注于
spring boot 1/5 and some of the great
spring boot 1/5和一些很棒的东西
stuff that Phil Webb mother and the rest
菲尔·韦伯母亲和其他人的东西
of the team
团队的
put out in that release and then we'll
在该版本中发布，然后我们将
show you some demos about how that works
向您展示一些有关其工作原理的演示
on pivotal Cloud Foundry is some
在关键的Cloud Foundry上是一些
interesting integration we're doing
我们正在做的有趣的整合
there inspired loosely by code centric
那里受到以代码为中心的宽松启发
on their spring boot admin tool which is
在他们的 spring boot 管理工具上
an open source tool that's available but
一个可用的开源工具，但
we we used it as a design point for the
我们将其用作设计点
integration that we're doing in in
我们正在进行的整合
spring mode and pc f so and then we'll
Spring 模式和pc f，然后我们将
finish that off my kind of just looking
完成我的那种看
ahead in the large not only for what's
大步向前不仅是为了什么
coming for next for spring boot interval
下一个 spring boot 间隔
cloud foundry but also kind of pulling
云铸造也有种拉
the lens back a teeny a little bit and
镜头向后退了一点
looking at some of the other interesting
看着其他一些有趣的东西
things in spring dome that have some
春天的圆顶里有一些东西
cool integration points to pivotal
很酷的整合指向关键
quadri so with that let's get started
Quadri，让我们开始吧
great so on spring point one for a
太好了，在春季点一
couple big themes there you know there
那里有几个大主题
was a bunch of improvements on air
在播放方面有很多改进
handling we made some incremental
处理我们做了一些增量
improvements to the actuator and some
执行器的改进和一些
improvements around data and as well as
数据方面的改进以及
a fair amount of improvement runtastic
相当多的改进
it's got a whole separate slide on that
在那上面有一张完整的幻灯片
the air handling bit is pretty
空气处理位很漂亮
straightforward
直截了当
we added some things around what we're
我们围绕我们添加了一些东西
calling failure analyzers basically it
基本上调用故障分析器
tries to simplify the diagnosis of some
试图简化一些诊断
common startup problems so rather than
常见的启动问题，而不是
just getting a nasty Java stack trace
只是讨厌的Java堆栈跟踪
we're trying to kind of analyze these
我们正在尝试分析这些
stack traces and give you not only a
堆栈跟踪，不仅给您
slightly more sensible error message but
稍微更明智的错误消息，但
try to give some remediation guidance my
尝试给我一些补救指导
favorite example is the one that bites
最喜欢的例子是咬人的例子
me in the tushy all the time which is I
我一直在泥泞中，这是我
start a process and oops the process was
启动一个进程，然后提示该进程是
already in use that port was already in
已经在使用中，该端口已经在使用中
used by somebody else and I kind of
被别人使用，我有点
forgot that I left uh you know maybe a
忘了我离开了，你知道
tomcat server or a jetty running on 8080
Tomcat服务器或在8080上运行的码头
I boot something it's trying to bound to
我引导它试图绑定的东西
8080 doesn't work so trying to get in
8080不起作用，因此尝试进入
front of that and give you better
前面，给你更好
quality error messages basically we
质量错误消息基本上我们
provide a number of these failure
提供一些这些失败
analyzers out of the box and they're
分析仪开箱即用
extensible so you can write your own the
可扩展的，因此您可以编写自己的
other interesting thing is the
另一个有趣的是
convention based error pages which is
基于约定的错误页面
kind of nice you're basically the
不错，你基本上是
ability to drop in a custom 404 page
能够放入自定义404页面
just kind of by convention so if you
按照惯例，所以如果您
wanted to register a custom 404 page you
想注册一个自定义的404页面
for example you just add it you drop a
例如，您只需添加它，然后删除
404 HTML into a path like source main
404 HTML进入类似于源main的路径
resource public error you know so it's
您知道的资源公共错误是
just kind of convention based and then
只是基于约定，然后
you can add in static HTML or a template
您可以添加静态HTML或模板
in that correct location and it just
在那个正确的位置，它只是
automatically creates a mapping so
自动创建映射，因此
that's pretty cool NIC's error page is a
这很酷NIC的错误页面是
little bit easier the data support
一点点的数据支持
basically is just saying that we are
基本上只是说我们
adding some new Auto configurations for
为添加一些新的自动配置
neo4j Couchbase Redis Redis spring data
neo4j Couchbase Redis Redis spring data
repositories and also hibernates 5.0 is
存储库，并且还休眠5.0是
now the default JPA provider and then
现在是默认的JPA提供程序，然后
lastly we just refreshed our
最后，我们刚刚刷新了
elasticsearch integration to include the
elasticsearch集成以包括
jest
笑话
j EST just quietly my favorite thing is
EST悄悄地我最喜欢的是
the actuator lah
执行器啦
point so that you you know can customize
点，以便您可以自定义
and contribute additional items so now
并贡献额外的物品，所以现在
out of the bus we support things like
下车我们支持诸如
the full or partial get information that
全部或部分获取信息
gets generated from a maydel maven a
从maydel maven生成
Gradle plugin build information that's
Gradle插件构建信息
generated from the spring boom a man in
春季繁荣产生的一个人
Gradle plugin and then any custom
Gradle插件，然后进行任何自定义
environment information any property
环境信息任何财产
that starts info dot star basically um
基本上启动信息点星
also we refined the forward slash
我们也完善了正斜线
metrics and point a little bit so that
指标并指出一点，以便
submissions can be sort of merged and
提交内容可以合并在一起，
grouped together it makes a lot easier
组合在一起使操作变得容易得多
to read on so that's just a quick recap
继续阅读，以便快速回顾
of some of the major features in 1.4 um
1.4 um中的一些主要功能
the other big thing was the testing
另一个大问题是测试
support so that that actually was pretty
支持，所以实际上很漂亮
a pretty good overhaul of what we what
对我们所做的事情进行了很好的大修
we did in one dot in earlier versions we
我们在早期版本中做到了一个点
introduced the notion of test slices on
介绍了测试切片的概念
and and things of that nature for one
和那种性质的东西
dot for now we're basically trying to
现在，我们基本上是在尝试
bring that auto configuration simplicity
使自动配置变得简单
to test it you know making it really
测试它，你知道它真的
easy to test a slice of your app so if
容易测试您的应用程序的一部分，所以如果
you know we're going to give you a slice
你知道我们会给你一块
for you know your data layer or perhaps
因为你知道你的数据层
a rest client or maybe Jason
一个休息的客户，或者也许是杰森
serialization the other thing that we're
序列化我们要做的另一件事
adding is you know basically Auto
添加是，您基本上知道自动
configured mocking so with the impact
配置了模拟，因此产生了影响
MVC test annotation you can kind of Auto
MVC测试注释可以自动
configure your way through through mock
通过模拟配置您的方式
MVC which is pretty cool spring brew can
MVC是很酷的春季啤酒罐
essentially create automatically create
本质上是自动创建
mock beans and manage the lifecycle for
模拟bean并管理其生命周期
tea with no setup so you know this isn't
没有设置的茶，所以你知道这不是
pretty it's a pretty decent overhaul of
这是一个相当不错的大修
the testing support on test classes and
测试课程的测试支持，以及
utilities are now provided in a
现在在
dedicated spring boot test and spring
专用 spring boot 测试和Spring
boot test auto configure jar file we've
引导测试自动配置jar文件
added things like search a JSON the
添加了诸如搜索JSON之类的内容
syrup and JSON path dependencies to the
糖浆和JSON路径对
test starter and provided a simpler sort
测试入门，并提供了更简单的排序
of unified axe spring boot test
斧头Spring 启动测试
annotation for use with Springs j-unit
用于Springs j-unit的注释
runner we can also now can auto
跑步者，我们现在也可以自动
configure a lot of these tests meaning
配置许多这些测试的含义
that you just have to you know do less
你只需要知道就少做些
configuration up for
配置为
we've also introduced dedicated
我们还介绍了专用
annotations for at JSON test at web MVC
Web MVC上的JSON测试的注释
test at rest client tests and at the
静态测试客户端测试和
data GPA test so that you can quickly
数据GPA测试，以便您可以快速
get to those slices that I referred to
到我提到的那些切片
before something's your data layer your
在您的数据层之前
West client Jason serialization things
西部客户Jason序列化的东西
like that and like I mentioned before
就像我之前提到的那样
there's also now some much better
现在也有一些更好的
mockito on integration so it makes it
集成上的模拟，使它成为现实
just a whole lot easier to mock or spy
只是更容易嘲笑或间谍
spring beads and of course the most
Spring 珠，当然最
requested and my personal favorite
要求和我个人的最爱
feature and of course our main
功能，当然还有我们的主要
evangelist Josh Long's
传教士乔希·朗（Josh Long）
favorite feature is banner images now if
现在最喜欢的功能是横幅图像
you have a picture of your CIO or your
您有您的CIO或您的照片
CFO you can definitely drop it into
首席财务官，您绝对可以放下
spring boot now as is and it will come
spring boot 现在就这样，它将来
right up on the boot boot screen you
就在启动启动屏幕上
know if you just need to try to help get
知道您是否只需要尝试帮助获得
your project funded you know you can you
您的项目有资金，您知道可以
can make sure you've got a picture of
可以确保您有一张
your CIO right there in the food screen
您的CIO就在食物屏幕上
they'll they'll love that or you can go
他们会喜欢的，否则你可以去
with the cyan cat which is my personal
和我个人的青色猫在一起
favorite in Josh's personal favorite but
Josh的个人收藏中的收藏，但
in either way you can just basically
无论哪种方式，您基本上都可以
take an arbitrary image file and it will
拍摄任意图像文件，它将
render an ASCII art banner which is
呈现ASCII艺术横幅
stupid cool just drop a banner gift
愚蠢的酷只是放下横幅礼物
better JPEG or gander banner PNG file in
更好的JPEG或gander标语PNG文件
your source main resources and it just
您的来源主要资源
automatically converts gets
自动转换获取
automatically converted to se which is
自动转换为se
just the coolest thing ever
只是有史以来最酷的事情
it's right hold on screen lag there but
这是正确的屏幕滞后
yeah so let's um that's just a super
是的，让我们来吧，这只是一个超级
quick recap of what's happened in 1.4 on
快速回顾一下1.4中发生的情况
now I'd like to turn it over to the
现在我想将其移交给
monitor to talk a little bit about the
监视一下有关
release that she's been working on on
释放她一直在努力
that has just been out for a little
刚刚出去了一点
while the spring boot 1.5 mother you
而 spring boot 1.5妈妈你
want to talk to us a little bit about
想和我们谈谈
some of the highlights yeah sure so one
是的一些亮点是的，所以肯定一个
of the exciting new features that was
令人兴奋的新功能
added to spring boot 1.5 was support for
在Spring Boot 1.5中添加了对
Apache caster for those of you who
阿帕奇脚轮适合那些谁
haven't heard of a Patrick Africa it's a
没听说过帕特里克·非洲
distributed messaging system and one of
分布式消息传递系统和其中之一
the key differences between a Patrick
帕特里克·帕特里克之间的主要区别
rafter and the traditional message
after子与传统信息
brokers is that with a Patrick alpha you
经纪人是，有了Patrick Alpha，您
can actually go back and read matches
可以回去看比赛
because it's the consumers that are
因为是消费者
maintaining a pointer to the log of
维护指向日志的指针
messages whereas the traditional best
信息而传统的最好
workers once the message has been
消息一旦发送
produced by the producer it's basically
生产者生产的基本上
gone spring Casca is the project that
春季卡斯卡（Casca）消失了，
provides string core concepts to Casca
向Casca提供字符串核心概念
based messaging systems and string boot
基于消息的系统和字符串引导
built on top of that by providing auto
通过提供自动
configuration for spring Tosca it's
Spring 托斯卡配置是
super easy to now get started with your
现在超级容易上手
after project and spring boot and I'm
在项目和 spring boot 后，我
going to walk you through a quick demo
将带您快速演示
of how you can do this so let's switch
如何做到这一点，让我们切换
over to the demo right before we only
就在我们之前进行演示
had it available as part of spring
春天有货吗
integration right now it's you can get
现在就可以集成
to the you can get your copy right from
您可以直接从
spring boot yes that's correct
spring boot 是的，这是正确的
so now it's the first-class citizen and
所以现在是头等公民
you can directly configure your swing
您可以直接配置您的挥杆
Kafka has been good so what we have here
卡夫卡一直很好，所以我们在这里
is a very simple screen boot application
是一个非常简单的屏幕启动应用程序
this is your application class it has a
这是您的应用程序类
regular spring boot application
常规的 spring boot 应用
annotations go over other enabled Africa
注释超过其他已启用的非洲
annotation in details a little later but
稍后详细注释，但
as you can see it has the main method
如您所见，它具有主要方法
which launches the Springer
这将启动Springer
location what we have here is a sender
位置我们在这里是一个发件人
class and the sender class gets injected
类和发送者类被注入
with a cough a template the Tasker
用咳嗽模板Tasker
template is provided to you by the
模板是由
string root Auto configuration it
字符串根自动配置
provides convenience methods for sending
提供方便的发送方法
messages to the class a broker and here
给班级经纪人和这里的消息
is configured to send string messages so
配置为发送字符串消息，以便
the send method over here which is
在这里的发送方法是
scheduled to run every second is going
计划每秒运行一次
to send messages using the cafe template
使用咖啡馆模板发送消息
on this topic so the topic is called
关于这个话题，所以这个话题叫做
string topic and the message that we're
字符串主题和消息
going to send is just message appended
要发送的只是附加的消息
with a counter just to give you an idea
与柜台只是为了给你一个想法
of what this demo is about it's more
这个演示的内容更多
about how string boot makes it easy for
关于字符串启动如何使它容易实现
you to configure Casca and get started
您可以配置Casca并开始使用
with it
用它
source is that deep diving into the
来源是，深入了解
internals of Apache car crash and what I
阿帕奇车祸的内部和我
have lined here lined up here is a few
在这里排队在这里排队
commits and we're starting off with the
提交，我们从
initial submit which is just sending the
最初提交的只是发送
string message and in this receiver
字符串消息，并在此接收器中
class we are going to consume that
上课我们要去消耗
message so the receiver class has a
消息，所以接收者类有一个
method that is annotated with at Kafka
在Kafka注释的方法
listener the ad Kafka listener
监听器广告Kafka监听器
annotation marks this method to be a
批注将此方法标记为
target of the Casca message listener on
Casca消息侦听器的目标
this topic so over here you would do
这个话题，所以在这里你会做
some to be of processing and decide what
一些要处理并决定什么
to do with the message but for the
与消息有关，但对于
purposes of the demo which is going to
该演示的目的是
log that message to enable the
记录该消息以启用
processing of this Kafka listener
该Kafka侦听器的处理
annotation we have for any ad enabled
我们为所有启用的广告提供的注释
after annotation over here on the
在这里的注释之后
application class since we run this app
应用程序类，因为我们运行了此应用程序
now I already have a casket broker and a
现在我已经有一个棺材经纪人和一个
zookeeper running in the background so
动物园管理员在后台运行
as you can see it's printing out
如您所见，它正在打印
received message one two three four as
收到消息一二三四为
the sender tended the
发件人倾向于
even over here which is listening which
即使在这里正在聆听
is receiving on this topic receives the
正在接收有关此主题的信息
message and crimp it out so that was
信息并卷曲出来，那是
pretty straightforward the one thing I
一件事我很简单
forgot to mention over here is to get to
忘了在这里提到是为了
drink after auto-configuration
自动配置后喝
you need to just add the string task
您只需要添加字符串任务
dependency either in your bomb XML if
依赖关系在您的炸弹XML中是否
you're using maven or in your builder
您正在使用Maven或在您的构建器中
trader if you're using Gradle
交易员，如果您使用Gradle
next let's look at a little bit about
接下来让我们看一下
how you can configure it
您如何配置它
Tasker so I'm going to check out the
塔斯克，所以我要去看看
next myth that I have here and the the
我在这里的下一个神话
difference between this and the previous
这和以前的区别
version that we had is that now the
现在的版本是
sender is configured to send an integer
发送方配置为发送整数
message over to the Kafka broker so I've
消息传递给Kafka经纪人，所以我已经
changed the topic name in topic and
更改了主题中的主题名称，并
instead of sending message of strings
而不是发送字符串消息
I'm just going to send the counter and
我要去寄柜台
now if I try to run this application so
现在，如果我尝试运行此应用程序，那么
as you can see since I've changed the
如您所见，因为我已经更改了
name of the topic my receiver is also
我的接收者的主题名称也是
listening on inch topic now render you
现在，您可以在英寸主题上收听
can see that I'm getting a serialization
可以看到我正在序列化
exception here because I'm trying to
这里的例外，因为我试图
send a value of class integer but the
发送类整数的值，但是
string serializer
字符串序列化器
fails to serialize that and one of the
无法序列化，其中之一
things that we get with spring boot is
我们用Spring Boot获得的东西是
the ability to configure properties very
非常有能力配置属性
easily through properties files it's a
轻松通过属性文件，这是一个
spring boot feature files configuration
Spring Boot功能文件配置
properties that lets you do that so we
可以让您做到的属性，因此我们
can easily fix this serialization as
可以轻松修复此序列化为
error that we are getting here by adding
通过添加我们到达这里的错误
these integer D serializers and
这些整数D序列化器和
serializers in our application
应用程序中的序列化器
properties files so now if I run
属性文件，所以现在如果我运行
location so that's the only change we
位置，这是我们唯一的变化
had to make in order to be able to send
必须做出才能发送
the integers message now if I send it
现在，如果我发送整数消息
you can see that the receiver is
您可以看到接收器是
printing out the integers message that
打印出整数消息
it got so it is simply easy to get
它得到了，所以很容易得到
started with rathotsava configure a few
开始于rathotsava配置一些
properties that are a bunch of other
一堆其他的属性
properties that you can configure and
您可以配置的属性以及
they're all under the string dot fast
他们都在字符串点下
sub tree things so you can look at the
子树的东西，所以你可以看看
documentation to figure out which a
文档找出哪个
property which are the property values
属性是属性值
inside okay cool we got some questions
里面不错，我们有一些问题
from the audience about this but we can
观众对此的看法，但是我们可以
let us address them in yet it's just at
让我们在里面解决他们，只是在
the end so those just have patience
最后，让那些人有耐心
we're seeing your questions we're just
我们正在看到您的问题，我们只是
going to address them at the end if you
如果你要解决的话
don't mind Joe the rest assured we've
不要介意乔，我们放心
you know if your injury stuff and we've
你知道如果你受伤的东西，我们已经
seen it so please feel free to keep
看过所以请随时保留
doing so but sorry mother--i um back to
这样做，但对不起母亲-我回到
me I guess
我猜我
great um so let's actually no sorry this
很好，所以实际上我们不要后悔
is the my conscience this is this is you
是我的良心，这是你
so whether you talk a little bit now
所以你现在是否说话
about the actuators in spring boot on as
关于Spring 启动器中的执行器
a preface for some of the integration of
一些整合的序言
work that we've done yes thanks Peter
我们所做的工作是，谢谢彼得
so one of the other things that we did
所以我们做的另一件事
as part of spring dude 1.5 was to change
作为春季花花公子1.5的一部分进行了更改
the security model or the spring boot
安全模型或 spring boot
actuators but before we get started with
执行器，但在我们开始之前
the security model I want to talk a
我想谈的安全模型
little bit about what the actuator and
关于执行器和
point are the actuator end points allow
点是执行器端点允许的
you to monitor and interact with your
您监控并与您互动
spring route application so if you have
春季路线申请，因此，如果您有
the spring boot actuator dependency
Spring Boot Actuator依赖性
added to your application you get a
添加到您的应用程序中，您将获得一个
number of built-in end points and you
内置端点的数量和您
could also add your own as you wanted to
也可以根据需要添加自己的
some examples of the built-in end points
内置端点的一些示例
that you get the health endpoint which
你得到健康终点
gives View application health info the
给View应用程序运行状况信息
environment end point which gives you
给您的环境终点
information about the spring environment
有关春季环境的信息
metrics trade audit events and the
指标交易审核事件和
number of other end points but we won't
其他终点数量，但我们不会
go into the details of each one as you
在您进入每个细节时
can tell a few of these endpoints can
可以告诉其中一些端点
potentially expose some sensitive
可能暴露一些敏感
information so your end end point
信息，因此您的终点
because it shows you the properties that
因为它向您显示了
are in your spring environment there
在你的春天环境中
could be something in there that you
可能是你里面的东西
probably don't want to be available to
可能不想
anyone who can access these end points
可以访问这些终点的任何人
so what was the security model for the
那么什么是安全模式
spring boot actuators before 1 5 I'm
1 5我之前的 spring boot 执行器
only going to talk about the actuators
只说说执行器
that exposed by a HTTP we can also have
通过HTTP公开的信息，我们也可以
JMX
JMX
he actually does expose over gmx but
他实际上确实暴露了gmx，但是
we're just going to talk about the MDC
我们只是要谈论MDC
and the HTTP ones over here so before 1
和HTTP在这里，所以在1之前
5 if you included the actuator
5（如果包括执行器）
dependency in your application or maybe
在您的应用程序中的依赖关系
you didn't include it intentionally but
您没有故意添加它，但是
it got added at some kind of transitive
它被添加在某种可传递的
dependency and say you didn't have
依赖，说你没有
security in your application at that
在您的应用程序中的安全性
point the actuator endpoint were all
指向执行器端点
open and by that I mean that anybody who
开放，我的意思是说，任何人
had access to the URL and you where your
有权访问该URL，而您在哪里
help and point was or where the endpoint
帮助和指向终点或终点
point was could hit that end point and
可以到达终点
see everything that the end point had so
看到终点的一切
if you unintentionally did this say it
如果您无意间这样说了
came in as a transitive dependency and
作为传递的依赖而来
you didn't want to add string security
您不想添加字符串安全性
to your application you could have ended
您的应用程序可能已经结束
up in a situation where you have these
在你有这些的情况下
potentially sensitive information all
所有潜在的敏感信息
exposed whereas if you added spring
暴露而如果您添加Spring
security you would get to login with a
安全性，您将使用
default username and password but not
默认的用户名和密码，但不是
everybody wants to add spring security
每个人都想增加Spring Security 性
and having default exposed end points
并具有默认的暴露端点
was probably
可能是
a little scary so in spring but--one
在春天有点吓人，但是-
five we decided that the evacuator end
五，我们决定撤离结束
point would be secure by default and by
默认情况下，通过
secure I mean only allow access to users
安全，我的意思是只允许访问用户
with the right permissions so now if you
具有正确的权限，所以现在如果您
have the actuator dependency and you
有执行器依赖性，您
don't have spring security you get an
没有Spring Security 保障，
unauthorized error when you try to
您尝试执行未经授权的错误
access the endpoint if you do have
如果您确实有访问端点
spring security you will get basic
Spring Security ，您将获得基本
authentication where you can login with
可以登录的身份验证
a default username and password to
默认的用户名和密码
access these endpoints so that basically
访问这些端点，以便基本上
prevents unintentional exposure of the
防止意外暴露
event points but say you do want to
事件点，但说你确实想
expose these endpoints you feel that
暴露这些端点，您感到
they're okay this information is okay to
他们可以，这个信息可以
be available to any user of your
可供您的任何用户使用
application or anyone any public user
应用程序或任何公共用户
you can disable the security for these
您可以禁用这些安全性
endpoints by simply setting a flag the
通过简单地设置一个标志
flag is called if management does
如果管理执行，则调用该标志
security enabled and if you set that to
启用安全性，并且如果将其设置为
false string boot will back off and you
错误的字符串启动将退出，您
can either leave the actuator endpoint
可以离开执行器端点
insecure or you can add your custom
不安全或您可以添加自定义
security configuration okay so the next
安全配置还可以，所以下一个
new thing that we added as part of 1.5
我们在1.5中添加的新内容
was the loggers endpoint and the lockers
是记录器端点和储物柜
endpoint is actually an insert in
端点实际上是一个插入
actuator endpoint and what it does is it
执行器端点及其作用是什么
allows you to view and modify the log
允许您查看和修改日志
levels in your application at runtime so
在运行时在应用程序中级别
you can get all the logger loggers in
您可以在其中获取所有记录器记录器
your application you can get an
您的应用程序可以获取
individual logger and you can change the
个人记录器，您可以更改
configuration for its specific logger
特定记录器的配置
I'm just going to show you a quick
我只想给你个快速的
example of how you can change the logger
如何更改记录器的示例
configuration at runtime
运行时配置
along with
随着
what the output is of the log our end
日志的输出是什么
point so again I just have a very simple
再说一遍，我只是非常简单
spring boot application over here and it
Spring Boot应用程序在这里和它
has the actuator dependency so if I go
有执行器依赖性，所以如果我去
to the clash loggers end point I can see
到冲突记录器的终点，我可以看到
adjacent of first it shows me the log
相邻的第一个向我显示日志
level so the loggers endpoint supports
级别，以便记录器端点支持
for the logging systems that are
用于记录系统
supported by spring boot so log back
spring boot 支持，因此请重新登录
jewel log4j - and it shows me the log
jewel log4j-它向我显示日志
levels that are possible to configure
可以配置的级别
for the current logging system that's
对于当前的日志记录系统
being used and along with that it shows
被使用，并显示
me the list of loggers and it shows me
记录器列表向我显示
the configured level for each other and
彼此配置的级别，以及
the affected level for that lover so I
那个恋人的受影响程度，所以我
can filter by a single number by doing
可以通过做一个单一的数字过滤
that and over here you can see that this
在那边，你可以看到
logger has the configured level null but
记录器的配置级别为null，但
an effective level that is given to it
赋予它的有效水平
by the logging system as info now if we
现在通过日志系统作为信息
want to change log level for this lover
想要更改此情人的日志级别
I can do a curve to the loggers in point
我可以给记录员画一条曲线
with the logger name and the data that
记录器名称和数据
I'm going to pass here I send believe me
我要经过这里，我寄给我相信
the configured level let's set it to
配置的级别将其设置为
debug because right now the the
调试，因为现在
effective level is info
有效水平是信息
so that's 200 and now if I view the
所以现在是200，如果我查看
logging configurations for this demo
此演示的日志记录配置
application other I can see that the
应用程序其他我可以看到
configured level has changed to debug
配置级别已更改为调试
and effectively the effective level is
有效的有效水平是
also a debug so this hopefully gives you
也是一个调试，所以这希望给你
an idea of how easy it is to change the
改变它有多容易的想法
logging configuration for your
您的日志记录配置
applications at runtime
运行时的应用程序
okay so now that we've seen a little bit
好吧，现在我们已经看到了一点
about the actuators and the new log has
关于执行器和新日志
been point that we've added let's move
我们已经添加了一点，让我们继续前进
on to the Cloud Foundry support that was
继续获得Cloud Foundry支持
added as part of one side so as part of
作为一侧的一部分添加，作为
physical Cloud Foundry 1.9 we added some
物理Cloud Foundry 1.9我们添加了一些
spring boot actuator integration through
Spring 引导执行器通过
the apps manager UI so if you deploy a
应用管理器用户界面，因此，如果您部署
spring boot 1.5 application to see cf-19
Spring Boot 1.5应用程序请参阅cf-19
you will see additional information
您将看到更多信息
about the application in the apps
关于应用程序中的应用程序
manager so a few things that you see
经理，你看到的几件事
that are listed here
在这里列出
the boot application is the boot icon
引导应用程序是引导图标
which can be an eye catcher to indicate
可以成为吸引眼球的对象
that a salute application augmented
敬礼的应用程序增加了
health information get information
健康信息获取信息
the runtime configuration of loggers
记录器的运行时配置
that we just saw can also be done to the
我们刚刚看到的也可以做到
apps manager UI and all these things are
应用管理器用户界面，所有这些都是
secured by the core authentication and
由核心认证和
authorization component of Cloud Foundry
Cloud Foundry的授权组件
which is the UA a so note the user
这是UA a，因此请注意用户
doesn't have to configure any additional
无需配置任何其他
security for the screens of actuators
执行器屏幕的安全性
when deployed to pivotal Cloud Foundry
部署到关键Cloud Foundry时
we can walk through the apps manager UI
我们可以浏览应用程序管理器用户界面
to take a look at how these things work
看一下这些东西是如何工作的
so what I have here is the ask manager
所以我这里是问问经理
running on feet over the web services or
通过Web服务或
PWS which is the hosted version of Cloud
PWS是Cloud的托管版本
Foundry
铸造厂
bicipital this is my actuator app that
这是我的执行器应用程序
it's the spring good one v app which is
这是春季的不错的v应用程序
pushed to PWS and the eye catcher that I
推向PWS和我的眼球
was talking about earlier is this is the
刚才说的是这个
spring boot icon so I can easily tell
spring boot 图标，所以我可以轻松分辨
that okay this application is a single
好的，这个应用程序是一个
application the instance held over here
应用这里保存的实例
is augmented with additional information
补充了更多信息
from the help endpoint you can configure
从帮助端点可以配置
your application to add some custom
您的应用程序添加一些自定义
health indicator so over here I just
健康指标，所以在这里我只是
added a custom hello world health
添加了自定义的Hello World Health
indicator but in your organization if
指标，但在您的组织中是否
you have some kind of custom services
您有某种定制服务
that you want to report the health or
您要报告健康状况或
you could add a custom health indicator
您可以添加自定义健康指标
another cool thing that has been
另一个很酷的事情是
integrated into the apps manager UI is
集成到应用管理器用户界面中的是
the good information so a lot of times
好信息很多次
you want to know which get Shalvis
你想知道哪个得到沙尔维斯
application with sales from and if
来自和如果有销售的申请
Angelita but with the apps manager you
Angelita，但有了应用程序管理器，您
can actually click on this link over
可以实际点击该链接
here and it'll take you to the git
在这里，它将带您进入git
commit that first application was served
提交第一个应用程序已送达
from so it gets with information from
从中获取信息
the either info and info actuator and to
信息和信息执行器，以及
do that you have to configure a few
这样做，您必须配置一些
things but I think those are mentioned
事情，但我认为那些被提到
in the docs which it does we'll talk
在文档中我们将讨论
about later in the settings tab you can
关于稍后在“设置”标签中，您可以
see the additional springboard
见附加的跳板
information from the info actuator
来自信息执行器的信息
currently it's in this raw JSON format
目前是这种原始JSON格式
but the mighty plans in the future to
但未来强大的计划
enhance the UI for this
为此改善UI
so again over here you
所以再次在这里
and see the get information the commit
并查看获取信息的提交
that this application was built from the
该应用程序是从
user etc the log tab has a substrate
用户等，日志选项卡上有底物
configurable logging level so if I go to
可配置的日志记录级别，所以如果我去
configure logging levels you can see the
配置日志记录级别，您可以看到
list of loggers that we previously saw
我们之前看到的记录器列表
for that singled out the single
为此，单身
application that was running standalone
独立运行的应用程序
you can sort of get filter the loggers
您可以对记录器进行过滤
by name so I'm gonna fill TARDIS to this
按名称，所以我要在其中填充TARDIS
schedule logger that I have over here
我在这里的日程表记录器
and change the logging level to debug
并更改日志记录级别以进行调试
your questions increase the size of your
您的问题会增加您的规模
text oh I don't know if you can do that
发短信哦，我不知道你能不能做到
in this screen yeah all right pretty
在这个屏幕上，好吧，漂亮
sure so as you can see I changed the
可以肯定的是，如您所见，我更改了
logging level for the federal lava from
联邦熔岩的测井水平从
info to diva and if I face that 2000 on
信息到女主角，如果我面对那2000
I'm special special to see if I can get
我特别特别看看我是否能得到
in the log sorry
在日志中对不起
it's exploding so it's going to take a
它正在爆炸，所以需要一个
sec in the meantime you can address one
在此期间，您可以处理一个
or two questions
或两个问题
oh no we got it okay let me see if I can
哦，不，我们知道了，让我看看是否可以
fit that model show all the third debug
拟合该模型显示所有第三次调试
and if you can see over here it's
如果你能看到这里
printing out these logging statements
打印这些日志记录语句
from my schedule dauber
从我的日程安排中
and these are only printed out in the
而这些仅打印在
debug mode so because I changed it to
调试模式，因为我将其更改为
people I am now getting those log
我现在正在获取这些日志的人
statements yeah so let's that's it for
声明是的，那么就这样吧
the PCF and actuator integration for
PCF和执行器集成
right now we have a few things coming up
现在我们有几件事
which Peter we'll get to in a second
彼得，我们稍后再讲
that's mother oh oh sorry I actually
那是妈妈哦，对不起，我真的
wanted to talk a little bit about how
想谈谈如何
this works so the way it works is we
这有效，所以它的工作方式是我们
have with the spring food 1.5 release
与春季食品1.5发布
the actuator module now includes
执行器模块现在包括
additional support or that gets
额外的支持或得到
activated when you deploy to a
部署到
compatible Cloud Foundry instance so the
兼容的Cloud Foundry实例，因此
same actuator endpoints that we see in a
我们在一个
regular spring food application they
他们定期春季食品应用
also get exposed what via the flash
也通过闪光灯暴露了什么
Cloud Foundry application pack and the
Cloud Foundry应用程序包和
reason why this is a separate path is
这是一条单独路径的原因是
because this path is protected
因为此路径受保护
I access tokens from the UAE and further
我从阿联酋访问令牌
it is protected by the cloud controllers
它受云控制器保护
role so only if you have certain roles
角色，所以只有当你有某些角色时
inside boundary like say space developer
内部边界就像说太空开发商
or base auditor and people who are
或基本审核员和
allowed to view this application on
允许在上查看此应用程序
Cloud Foundry only those roles get
只有这些角色才能获得Cloud Foundry
access to these actuator endpoints so it
可以访问这些执行器端点
is a transparent security integration by
是由
between apps manager and the UAA and
在应用管理器和UAA之间以及
cloud controllers which does not require
不需要的云控制器
any additional security configuration by
任何其他安全配置
the app developer a few other one five
应用程序开发人员另外五个
highlights that I want to go over were
我想过去的重点是
the addition of the audit events
审核事件的添加
endpoint so the audit events endpoint is
端点，因此审核事件端点为
another actuator and audit event get
另一个执行器和审核事件得到
recorded for authentication and
记录用于身份验证和
authorization events but you can also
授权事件，但您也可以
record your own events using the audit
使用审核记录您自己的事件
adventure posit ori now so now we have
现在冒险冒险ori，所以现在我们有了
jmx endpoint that allows you to query
jmx端点，可让您查询
previously recorded audit events over
先前记录的审核事件
GMX
GMX
and we also have a slash audit events
我们还进行了大幅的审核活动
MVC endpoint to get these events as far
MVC端点以获取这些事件
as elder support goals we now provide
现在我们作为老年人的支持目标
auto configuration for any elder
自动配置任何长者
compliant servers and for easily testing
兼容服务器并易于测试
your LDAP in your application we provide
您在应用程序中提供的LDAP
an in-memory LDAP from unbound ID which
来自未绑定ID的内存中LDAP
allows you to test our app without
允许您测试我们的应用程序而无需
really needing a real LDAP server
确实需要一个真正的LDAP服务器
great thank you mother
妈妈，谢谢你
okay um let's talk a little bit let's
好吧，让我们谈一点，让我们
look ahead a little bit mm-hmm um and we
向前看一点，嗯，我们
have a ton of questions so mother and I
有很多问题，所以我和妈妈
are trying to speed through this quickly
正在尝试快速解决这个问题
so that we can get to those I've been
这样我们就可以去那些我去过的地方
researching some of them well while you
在您研究其中的某些内容时
were talking so we've got a few answers
在说话，所以我们有几个答案
in queue already um so yeah so let's
在排队中，嗯，是的，让我们
look ahead a little bit arm and we are
向前看一点手臂，我们是
very interested in excited Phil and the
对兴奋的菲尔和
rest of the team are really hard work on
团队的其他成员真的很努力
string book to zero obviously that will
字符串簿为零显然会
come out and be released subsequent to
出来并在之后被释放
Spring Framework 5.0 SGA release of
Spring Framework 5.0 SGA发布
course so just looking ahead spring boot
当然，所以只是展望 spring boot
- OH
-哦
irrespective of a pebble Cloud Foundry
不管是卵石铸造厂
integration obviously this is going to
集成显然这将
be the release that supports the the
是支持
Spring Framework revival reacted
Spring Framework 复兴反应
concepts and the spring web blocks web
概念和Spring Web Blocks Web
framework reactive web framework this is
框架反应式Web框架，这是
what's going to make your full stack
什么会使您的堆栈全满
reactive app a little bit easier to
反应性应用程序更容易
bootstrap you know typical sort of
引导程序，您知道典型的
spring boot auto-configuration uh so you
Spring Boot自动配置嗯，所以你
know mechanisms will be available as you
知道机制将在您可用时
might expect obviously you're getting
可能显然你会得到
the rest of the team have been very
团队的其他成员非常
closely tracking Java nine released for
密切跟踪发布的Java九
some time now and we will be supporting
现在有一段时间，我们将支持
John nine in spring boots - oh of course
约翰九在 spring boot -当然哦
on Java EE eight you know the Jade some
在Java EE八上，​​您知道Jade的一些知识
jsr is obviously server servlet or four
jsr显然是服务器servlet或四个
O's and exciting jsr for sure is that a
O和令人兴奋的jsr肯定是
fest you know good chunk of the Java
祝您知道Java的好知识
universe there as well as being
那里的宇宙以及
validation so those are things were
验证，所以这些都是
definitely tracking very closely and
绝对非常紧密地跟踪
will be supported in boot - oh um the
将在启动时受支持-哦，
other thing of course is uh you know
另一件事当然是
well there's you know this is so
好吧，你知道这是事实
typically a bit of a rolling delivery
通常是滚动交付
but you know at GH on every spring boat
但是你知道每年春天的船上的GH
Udo
你做
we'll start by focusing on sort of the
我们将从专注于
major generation updates of various
各代的主要更新
spring projects so you know a spring
春天计划，所以你知道春天
integration 500 or a spring session 200
整合500或春季课程200
or something of that nature as opposed
或与之相反的性质
to a point release perhaps or you know
也许你知道
something something more minor I'm so
我更小一些
you can expect
你可以期待
some of the major top-level spring
一些主要的顶级春季
projects to be boot - Olaf I'd right at
要启动的项目-Olaf我就在
ready release also the main sort of I
准备发布也是我的主要类型
think answer you know when I was
想想答案，你知道我什么时候
originally chatting with till web team
最初与直到网络团队聊天
Brian D shows to feign rawson and
布赖恩D展示假装罗森和
everyone and you know I kind of asked
大家，你知道我有点问
them I was like what what is you know
他们我就像你知道什么
why what's what sort of unique about the
为什么有什么独特的
Spring Framework reactive approach you
Spring Framework反应性方法
know why would someone sort of maybe
知道为什么有人会
choose us as opposed to some of the
选择我们而不是一些
other reactive options out there and I
其他反应性选择，我
mean one of the really strong answers
意味着真正有力的答案之一
that's coming through is the ability to
这是通过能力
plug and play the the different runtimes
即插即用不同的运行时
available so as you may or may not be
可用，无论您是否可能
aware of patchy Tomcat is certainly
知道斑驳的Tomcat肯定是
working hard on you may not even realize
努力工作甚至可能没有意识到
actually that 75% of the Apache Tomcat
实际上这是Apache Tomcat的75％
codebase is written by pivotal employees
代码库由关键员工编写
I think there's three or four people if
我想如果有三四个人
you we've added some some you folks
你我们增加了一些你们
lately but pivotal is actually employees
最近但关键是员工
are actually responsible for majority of
实际上负责大多数
Apache Tomcat code and they're hard at
Apache Tomcat代码，他们很难
work on unreactive about non-blocking
对非阻塞不反应
servlet implementations right obviously
servlet实现正确
there's reactor nettie if you work with
如果您使用，有反应堆网
the MIDI before that's always popular
之前的MIDI一直很流行
when jetty and JBoss is undertow so and
当码头和JBoss受到追捧时，
possibly others you know these are the
可能其他人您知道这些是
reactive runtimes that we're going to be
我们将成为的反应性运行时
focusing on for for spring dot spring
专注于Spring 点Spring
boot - oh great
开机-太好了
um so um so this is exciting a mother
嗯，嗯，这让母亲很兴奋
and I were talking about this yesterday
我昨天在谈论这个
what's coming ahead just for the the
即将到来的是什么
actuator integration that she was
她曾经是执行器集成
showing you um you know Ben Hale and the
向您展示您知道本·黑尔（Ben Hale）和
rest of the team are hard at work on the
团队的其他成员都在努力工作
next incremental set of boot actuators
下一组启动执行器
and surfacing those in pivotal cloud
并在关键云中覆盖
boundaries apps manager which is the
边界应用程序管理器
user interface that you were seeing
您所看到的用户界面
earlier actually to be completely
实际上早先是完全
technically accurate mother was showing
技术上准确的妈妈正在展示
you the apps manager from pivotal web
您来自关键网络的应用程序管理器
services which is our hosted public
我们托管的公共服务
cloud instance of Cloud Foundry that's
Cloud Foundry的云实例
available to any spring boot developer
适用于任何Spring Boot开发人员
if you sign up you get I think about
如果您注册，您就会明白
eighty seven dollars a pretty trial
八十七美元的审判费。
credit or something one Matt so it's a
信用或某事马特，所以这是一个
great place for spring blue apps test
春季蓝色应用程序测试的好地方
dev environments spirit capacity for CI
CI的开发环境精神能力
build that sort of thing so that's what
建立这样的东西，这就是
she was showing you we're working on
她向你展示我们正在努力
that next set of spring mood actuator
下一套春天心情执行器
things like heat dump thread dump and
像热转储线程转储和
trace are currently what's in plan but
跟踪当前正在计划中，但是
you know we're not honored to stand
你知道我们不荣幸站起来
committed there yet we're still kind of
承诺在那里，但我们仍然有点
going back and forth and deciding what
来回去决定什么
makes the most sense for the next
对下一次最有意义
release the heat dump is pretty
放出的热量很漂亮
straightforward this just returned to
直截了当，这才回到
gzip compressed heat dump file dumps
gzip压缩热转储文件转储
pretty straightforward makes bread dump
简单明了的面包
trace just gives you the last
跟踪只给您最后
information the last 100 HTTP requests
信息最近的100个HTTP请求
by default and the trace information in
默认情况下，跟踪信息在
there so those are coming soon on to a
在那里，那些很快就会到
new pedal Cloud Foundry release near you
您附近的新踏板Cloud Foundry发布
arm and on the fullness of time we're
手臂和时间的充裕，我们
certainly going to be going for the
肯定会去的
complete set of actuators and surfacing
整套执行器和堆焊
those in the apps manager a user
应用管理器中的用户
interface so basically the only two that
界面，所以基本上只有两个
we're not going to instrument are
我们不会去仪器
shutdown and log file and mother
关闭和日志文件和母亲
yesterday to me explain why which makes
昨天给我解释为什么
perfect sense because you can shut down
完美的感觉，因为你可以关闭
the the boot app from within Apps
在Apps内启动应用程序
Manager so you don't necessarily need to
经理，所以您不一定需要
shut down endpoint yourself on the loan
自行关闭端点借贷
file
文件
well longer Gator in PCF does an amazing
PCF中更长的Gator效果惊人
job of streaming logs from multiple
来自多个流日志的工作
spring boot instances in multiple
Spring Boot实例多个
containers across the PCF system and
PCF系统中的容器和
making it kind of appear as one log
使它看起来像一个日志
stream we call that component moderator
流，我们称之为组件主持人
so there's no need really to dump out a
因此没有必要真正丢弃
log file when you're running on PCF
在PCF上运行时的日志文件
blogger Gator does that for you
博客Gator为您做到这一点
automatically also we're looking at the
自动地，我们也在看
PCF metrics team if you're unfamiliar
PCF指标小组（如果您不熟悉）
with PCF metrics I'll talk a little bit
关于PCF指标，我会讲一点
more about it in a minute but it's just
只需一分钟即可了解更多信息，但这仅仅是
kind of some operational data container
某种操作数据容器
metrics you know network in out you know
您知道的指标网络知道
CPU usage that sort of thing um in those
CPU使用率在那些
metrics are going to get piped from
指标将通过管道传递
spring mood actuator if you define
如果定义，则为春季心情执行器
custom metrics we're working them PCF
自定义指标，我们正在使用这些指标
metrics team is working on surfacing
指标小组正在研究
those in the PCF metrics user user
PCF指标用户中的用户
experience which is really cool some
体验真的很棒
things that are kind of more on the
更像是
radar not you know not even you know
雷达，你不知道，你也不知道
remotely committed to yet or anything
远程承诺尚未完成
like that but we're we're kind of
那样，但是我们有点
using about and really want to hear from
使用并真的希望听到
you frankly we're been Heil has been
坦率地说，我们一直在Heil
considering the reactive actuator
考虑电抗器
endpoints
终点
we're also looking at a micro services
我们也在研究微服务
dashboard or Dino's J works
仪表板或Dino的J作品
Josh long get a cool Lebanon that a few
乔什（Josh）长期得到一个很酷的黎巴嫩
a few weeks ago the spring tip series
几周前的春季贴士系列
there's an awesome little visualization
有一个很棒的可视化
dashboard for your micro services we're
您的微服务的仪表板
kind of looking at that as well but
看起来也一样
really what we do want to do is hear
我们真正想做的就是听到
from you if you are Springville user and
如果您是Springville用户，并且
a pivotal Cloud Foundry user or a
关键的Cloud Foundry用户或
pivotal Web Services user um traverse
关键的Web服务用户um遍历
that link and you can apply to have an
该链接，您可以申请拥有一个
interview with our user experience team
采访我们的用户体验团队
and they'll give you a $75 gift card for
他们会给您一张75美元的礼品卡
participating the forum is literally
参加论坛实际上是
like three fields but if you use these
像三个字段，但是如果您使用这些
two things together now is your chance
两件事在一起现在是您的机会
to sort of influence product management
影响产品管理
to run this directly and have your voice
直接运行并发出声音
heard we're very very interested in
听说我们非常感兴趣
talking to you cool so what kool lens
和你说话很酷，那么什么傻瓜镜头
back just a teeny a little bit from just
回来只是一个小小的
sort of what's the spring boots and have
spring boot 是什么
been and Cloud Foundry scenario when you
当过Cloud Foundry场景时
widen the lens to to a little bit wider
将镜头扩大到稍微宽一点
in spring 'dom there's something that
在春季，“ dom中有一些东西
we've done with with some some great
我们已经完成了一些很棒的
spring cloud integration that you may or
您可以或的 Spring Cloud 集成
may not be familiar with you've probably
可能对您不熟悉
heard of it by this point but spring
到现在为止听说过它，但是春天
cloud services is basically the
云服务基本上是
server-side components of eureka netflix
Eureka Netflix的服务器端组件
OSS eureka history and our config server
OSS eureka历史记录和我们的配置服务器
which is sort of your your gate or happy
这就是您的大门或开心之门
for fault as a as a configuration
作为配置的故障
service of the network and these are a
网络服务，这些都是
hundred percent bosch managed PCF manage
博世百分百管理的PCF管理
instances so no longer do you have to
实例，所以您不再需要
sort of install and configure and even
某种安装和配置，甚至
manage on eureka hystrix config server
在尤里卡hystrix配置服务器上管理
over you know multiple multiple
在你知道多个倍数
containers this is now as an extremely
容器，这现在是一个极端
recently live in public beta on pivotal
最近住在关键的公开测试版中
web services so you want to give it a
网络服务，所以您想给它一个
spin you just go right to run that
旋转你就可以运行它
pivotal do you can give it a shot on
关键的，你可以试一试吗
pretty cool stuff we aren't thinking
我们没有想到的很酷的东西
about all kinds of crazy things for the
关于各种疯狂的事情
future and we want to hear from you what
未来，我们希望听到您的消息
do you think on what sounds interesting
你觉得听起来有趣吗
to you some of the things that are being
给你一些正在发生的事情
talked about on in product management
在产品管理中谈到
right now we're talking about things
现在我们在谈论事情
like composite
像复合
backends for configuration server where
后端的配置服务器
you can mix maybe a hashing Court vault
您可以混合使用散列式法院 Vault
and get together we're looking at direct
聚在一起，我们正在寻找直接
support for spring cloud dataflow as
支持Spring Cloud Data Flow为
part of spring cloud services those
Spring Cloud 服务的一部分
runtime again those runtime pieces you
再次运行时那些运行时碎片
know usually when you're we're talking
通常知道你在什么时候我们在说话
about some provide services we're
关于一些我们提供的服务
usually more talking kind of about the
通常更多地谈论
the server-side bits for now
现在服务器端的位
we're also coincidentally investigating
我们也在偶然地调查
how to make that easier for for client
如何使客户更轻松
development but that's another topic
发展，但这是另一个话题
other things supporting some of the new
其他支持一些新事物的东西
very recent Pinto Cloud Foundry features
Pinto Cloud Foundry的最新功能
that have hit the market like surgical
像外科手术一样进入市场的
routing or the new container to
路由或新容器
container networking stack also may be
容器网络堆栈也可能是
improving the collaboration around our
改善我们周围的合作
service registry often we found that
服务注册表通常我们发现
teams want to collaborate in ways that
团队希望以某种方式进行协作
don't necessarily just map to CF orgs
不一定只是映射到CF组织
and spaces so that folks might want to
和空间，以便人们可能想要
actually be able to see service
实际能够看到服务
registries from other groups so we're
来自其他团体的注册表
considering some arbitrary linking
考虑一些随意的链接
contests to a lot of people to more
比赛吸引了很多人
easily collaborate and then another
轻松协作，然后再进行协作
thing on the sheet' evolving the config
工作表上的东西不断发展的配置
server into a slightly more
服务器多一点
self-contained configuration management
独立的配置管理
product so you know maybe we would
产品，所以您知道也许我们会
actually provide a back-end figuration
实际提供了后端图形化
database rather than you know sort of
数据库，而不是您知道的那种
bring your own kits or bring your own
带上自己的装备或带上自己的装备
vault and lots of other things to sort
保险库和其他很多东西
of make it a little bit more or turnkey
使更多或交钥匙
you know even a little more turnkey last
你知道最后一点交钥匙
thing this is one I'm personally most
这是我个人最喜欢的一件事
excited about and I think it's really
我很兴奋，我认为这真的
interesting is the dynamic routing for
有趣的是
the service registry where we might look
我们可能会看到的服务注册表
at auto provisioning and pairing Zul
在自动配置和配对Zul时
instances for your Eureka instances you
您的尤里卡实例
can do things like content based routing
可以做基于内容的路由之类的事情
and actually would be the foundation of
实际上是
an insane amount of futures other
疯狂的期货其他
features you know things like canary
您知道的功能，例如金丝雀
deploys and and stuff like that I'm all
部署和诸如此类的东西
those you know in some aspects that are
在某些方面您知道的是
already supported of course in
当然已经在
table-cloth foundry but that's basically
台布铸造厂，但这基本上是
as you can see a pretty vibrant and
如您所见，一个充满活力的
exciting roadmap for Spring cloud
Spring Cloud激动人心的路线图
services and we think this is pretty
服务，我们认为这很漂亮
unique in the market so we're looking to
市场上独一无二的，所以我们期待
hear from you
听到你的消息
on few other things again pulling the
在其他一些事情上再次拉
lens back a little bit wider let's shift
镜头后退一点点，让我们转移
the focus away from spring cloud
焦点远离春天的云
services for a second and just talk very
服务一秒钟，只是说很
briefly
短暂地
about some of the work they're doing on
关于他们正在进行的一些工作
the PCF metrics team and with spring
PCF指标小组并在春季
clouds specifically with spring cloud
专门与 Spring Cloud
sleuth this is our framework that sort
侦探这是我们的框架
of wraps some of the different racing
包装了一些不同的赛车
capabilities hopper spring cloud and the
功能料斗Spring 云和
idea is that if if you've enabled that
想法是，如果您启用了
and you're basically PCF metrics which
而您基本上是PCF指标
is sort of your operational data view
是您的运营数据视图
and shows off things like container
并炫耀诸如容器之类的东西
metrics CPU memory disk usage Network
指标CPU内存磁盘使用情况网络
metrics you know how many requests per
您知道每个指标有多少个请求的指标
second that sort of stuff application
第二种东西的应用
events you know nap is created updated
您知道创建午睡的事件已更新
starts off scratch application logs you
开始从头开始应用程序日志您
know that that sort of PCF metrics in
知道这种PCF指标
like a two-second nutshell there but you
像是两秒钟的摘要，但是你
know that's your operational data and
知道那是您的运营数据，
the idea would be that if you turned on
这个想法是，如果你打开
some visit in tracing PCF metrics is
跟踪PCF指标的一些访问是
going to detect that data those fan IDs
要检测那些风扇ID的数据
and those trace ID is automatically in
那些跟踪ID会自动出现在
the logs and start to integrate it into
日志并开始将其集成到
this sort of user interface which is
这种用户界面是
kind of presented as a climb series well
有点像是攀登系列
as you can see there in the screenshot
如您在屏幕截图中所见
so um when you're especially when you're
所以当你特别是当你
doing micro service architecture where
做微服务架构的地方
you've got potentially lots of different
你可能会有很多不同
services understanding the complete call
服务了解完整的通话
graph latency for each component it's
每个组件的图形延迟
going to be really important so this is
真的很重要，所以这是
going to help you find all the logs that
将帮助您找到所有的日志
have that trace ID you know what
具有该跟踪ID，您知道什么
services did it touch how long what was
服务触及了多长时间
the timing on that and of course the
时间安排，当然
call hierarchy so this is some work that
调用层次结构，所以这是一些工作
that hasn't hit the market yet but it's
那还没有上市，但是
stuff where we're very actively working
我们非常积极工作的地方
on and it's fairly mature and certainly
并已经相当成熟，当然
would love your feedback on um yeah
希望您对um的反馈
great so um let's move on yeah let's
太好了，让我们继续前进，是的，
let's move on to our last line and let's
让我们继续进行最后一行，
start to take some questions folks we've
开始问一些我们已经问过的问题
got about ten minutes left and a ton of
还剩十分钟左右，还有一吨
questions so this is great thank you for
问题，这太好了，谢谢
all that um let me start right off um by
嗯，让我马上开始
addressing the wrong link there that
解决那里的错误链接
parently there was a erroneous link on
父母上有一个错误的链接
the documentation so I'm just displaying
文档，所以我只是显示
that now on that's the correct link for
现在，这是正确的链接
the spring boot actuator Docs and you
Spring Boot ActuatorDocs和您
know if you're just if you're a Google
知道您是否只是Google
fan you can just you know Google for
粉丝，你就可以知道Google
action
行动
Springwood actuator on Doc's pibil do
Doc的pibil上的Springwood执行器
and you'll get right to it
你会正确的
that's a that's another way to get to
那是到达的另一种方式
acquit pretty quickly great and once
很快就无罪释放
like I just got to keep track of a lot
就像我只是要跟踪很多
of questions folks I just need to keep
我只需要保留的问题
track of some of these things on a good
很好地跟踪其中的一些东西
question of what versions of software
什么软件版本的问题
doing eating to be able to get all this
做饭才能得到所有这些
good stuff or for the actuator
好东西或作动器
integration on basically this is spring
整合基本上是春天
boot one five one I think can teach it
引导一五一我认为可以教它
one not yeah so it's been good one five
一个不是，所以这是很好的一五个
one and cf-19 that's right and if you
一个和cf-19对，如果您
want to play around with it you can also
想要玩它，你也可以
use CWS that's a little web services
使用只是Web服务的CWS
which is the whole street version and i
这是整个街道的版本，我
believe you can sign up for the free
相信您可以免费注册
trial and deploy your spring to 1.5 one
试用并将您的spring部署到1.5
app to it thank you arm okay and notice
适用于它的应用程序，谢谢您的手臂还可以，并注意
someone else saying that the survey link
有人说调查链接
was down will will address that right
沮丧将解决这一权利
away and get that survey link back up if
离开并获得该调查链接，如果
you're interested in the user interface
您对用户界面感兴趣
to interview um just one second and yeah
采访一秒钟，是的
hopefully we'll get that back up very
希望我们会把它备份
quickly so maybe check back in about
很快，所以也许回来看看
five minutes thank you for commenting
五分钟谢谢你的评论
that by the way okay great so yeah I
好的，太好了，是的，我
appreciate you calling it out thank you
谢谢你喊出来谢谢
for reporting the blog um let's see um
用于报告博客，让我们来看看
question was there were some conquer
问题是有人征服了吗
questions earlier to I'm going to get to
我要早点问的问题
that in just a second
只需一秒钟
there was one question on how this
对此有一个问题
spring boot on PWS differ differ from
PWS上的春季引导与
spring boot microservices so the answer
spring boot 微服务，所以答案
to that is I mean spring boot can be
就是说我的意思是 spring boot 可以
used to create microservices by itself a
用于独自创建微服务
spring cloud is an extension to spring
春天的云是春天的延伸
boot that provides you a bunch of
引导为您提供了一堆
tooling and infrastructure to help you
工具和基础架构可以为您提供帮助
to microservices more easily um running
微服务更容易运行
spring boot on typical web services the
典型Web服务上的Spring Boot
the difference you know I mean are micro
你知道我的意思是微的差异
services are in architecture and typical
服务是架构中的，典型的
web services is a deployment platform
Web服务是一个部署平台
really so
真的是这样
you're sort of saying what's different
你在说什么不同
about apples and oranges they're a
关于苹果和橙子，他们是
little teeny bit it's just when you're
一点点的青春，只是当你
running Springville and pivotal web
运行Springville和枢纽网络
services you're just running it on our
您正在我们的服务上运行的服务
public cloud foundry instance and you
公共云铸造实例，您
know just doing the usual cloud things
知道只是做平常的云事情
right you know you pay for what you use
知道您为使用的商品付费
you know you're obviously not deploying
你知道你显然没有部署
to a local server you're deploying
到要部署的本地服务器
something remote and what do you deploy
远程的东西，你部署什么
whether it's a micro service or not is
不管是微服务还是
sort of up to you right so hopefully
有点取决于你，所以希望
that hopefully that helps question where
希望这有助于质疑在哪里
can you get the survey link from um it
你能从嗯那里得到调查链接吗
should it is in the if you look in the
如果它在如果你看
attachments and links section of your
您的附件和链接部分
user interface there is a link to it
用户界面上有一个链接
someone just reported however that there
有人刚刚报告说
was an issue with D but an issue with
是D的问题，但是是D的问题
the survey link for some reason but
调查链接出于某些原因，但
we're will get that back up for you in
我们将在您那里为您备份
no time so maybe just check back a
没时间了，所以也许就回来看看吧
little little later today give us a few
今天稍晚一点给我们一些
minutes and we'll we'll make sure that
分钟，我们将确保
that's up for you if you're interested
如果您有兴趣，这适合您
in an interview we very much like to
在采访中，我们非常想
hear from you
听到你的消息
great yeah you're welcome yeah totally
太好了，不客气
and thank you for reporting it um okay
谢谢你的举报
great um is there another question is
很好，还有另一个问题是
there an out-of-the-box Splunk
开箱即用的Splunk
integration for longs metrics admin
集成多头指标管理员
changes for things okay a little bit of
事情的变化还可以
syntax much there but I think you're
那里的语法很多，但我认为你是
asking for out-of-the-box Splunk
要求开箱即用的Splunk
integration um
积分um
total Cloud Foundry I has a has its own
我拥有的Cloud Foundry总有自己的
sort of log relation capabilities but I
某种日志关系功能，但我
believe there is some Splunk integration
相信有一些Splunk集成
personally I would have to double check
我个人必须仔细检查
that on network uh pivotal dot IO to
网络上的关键点IO到
make absolutely sure I have a vague
绝对确定我含糊
recollection of it but I don't want to
回忆起来，但我不想
give you the wrong answer there so you
给你错误的答案，所以你
might just want to go to network top
可能只想转到网络顶部
video and take a look for any sort of a
视频，看看任何形式的
Splunk integrations file um but we do
Splunk集成文件um，但我们确实
some provides some log aggregation
一些提供一些日志聚合
capabilities I think we're Splunk shines
我认为我们是Splunk的能力
is a little bit more on the log analysis
在日志分析上要多一点
fronts which is not what longer gator
前沿不再是鳄鱼
does so kind of depends what you're
取决于您的实际情况
looking for really um you know if you're
寻找真的，你知道你是否
kind of grappling with that decision I
我有点为那个决定而苦恼
would take a look at the logger Gator
来看看记录仪鳄鱼
documentation documentation and see if
文档文档，看看是否
that has sort of you're just enough
那种你就足够了
feature set or whether you need
功能集或是否需要
something that is really full-blown log
真正成熟的东西
analysis ah let's see okay hold on just
分析啊，让我们看看还好吧
a second
一秒
little questions coming in fast all
快来的小问题
right I'm getting the top of the stack
对了，我已经到了栈顶
and I feel like I'm being unfair to some
我觉得我对某些人不公平
of the people that ask questions at the
的人在
beginning so I'm now going to go to the
开始，所以我现在要去
bottom of the question stack where we
问题堆栈的底部
had a few questions on on Spring Fair
在春季博览会上有几个问题
patchy Kafka which are engineered Gary
拼凑而成的Kafka，由Gary设计
Russell was very kind enough to answer
罗素非常友善
back channel for me on and there was a
回到我的频道，有一个
question about spring for patchy Kafka
关于斑点卡夫卡的春天的问题
was can you create a new listener where
您可以创建一个新的侦听器吗
the topic is defined at runtime and the
该主题是在运行时定义的，
answer that is yes you can either create
回答是可以创建
a Kafka messagelistener container object
Kafka messagelistener容器对象
on or if you're using spring integration
或如果您正在使用Spring Integration
you can use the domain-specific language
您可以使用特定于域的语言
of DSL there's a dynamic flow
DSL的动态流
registration capability there so if
那里的注册能力，如果
you're using the DSL it's dynamic flow
您正在使用DSL，它是动态流
registration if you're you know I'm not
如果您知道我不是，请注册
using the DSL and you're coding java on
使用DSL，并且您正在对java进行编码
the command line you create a Kafka
您创建Kafka的命令行
message listener container object start
消息侦听器容器对象开始
to the log name there but spring is not
到那里的日志名称，但是spring没有
known for short names
以短名而闻名
tee hee hee hee hee um so hopefully that
tee hee hee hee hee um希望如此
helps you out there and another question
可以帮助您，还有另一个问题
is there a spring boot starter Kafka I
有 spring boot 启动器Kafka I
think you mean is there a starter for
以为你的意思是有一个入门
spring for Apache Kafka and the answer
Spring for Apache Kafka和答案
that is yes on sprout start spring bio
那是对芽开始春天生物
there is a checkbox for spring for
有一个Spring 复选框
Apache Kafka that is the starter I think
我认为Apache Kafka是入门
or my am I going nuts mother or is that
还是我要疯了，还是那个
is that I think the the spring goes data
是我认为春天来了
that they might be asking about is like
他们可能会问的就像
the spring good data actuator or all
Spring 良好的数据执行器或全部
those kind of things that we have and I
我们和我拥有的那种东西
don't think we have one for Apache kept
不要以为我们有一个适合Apache的
by the thing that you're talking about
通过你在说的东西
on Stratos fingered iOS you can add your
在Stratos手指iOS上，您可以添加
card for dependency when you are
当你是依赖卡
creating that application on startups
在启动时创建该应用程序
finger dial but I'm not sure about the
手指拨盘，但我不确定
Apache car charger I don't think it's
阿帕奇车载充电器我不认为这是
there okay thank you for appreciating
好的，谢谢你的赞赏
nice cash
不错的现金
recommend and why a question on spring
推荐，以及为什么对春天有疑问
on RabbitMQ which would you
公鸡在RabbitMQ上，你会
recommend and why um that's one of my
推荐，为什么是我的其中之一
favorite questions lately actually and I
最近我和我最喜欢的问题
think mother had nailed it when she said
以为妈妈说的话就钉了
that caca is really designed and built
caca是真正设计和制造的
around a very particular somewhat narrow
周围非常狭窄
set of use cases but it really kicks
用例集，但确实可以解决
butt for those use cases on you know
您知道的那些用例的对接
it's a durable message store so you you
这是一个持久的消息存储库，所以您
have a cursor in it and you have this
有一个光标，你有这个
concept of being able to kind of go back
能够回溯的概念
in time and say hey what were the last
及时说嘿，最后是什么
bunch of messages like your consumer
一堆消息，例如您的消费者
code needs to keep track of where the
代码需要跟踪
cursor is whereas in traditional
光标是，而在传统
enterprise message focused like RabbitMQ
专注于RabbitMQ的企业消息
perhaps or something else when you DQ a
当您进行DQ
message when a consumer J'Accuse a
消费者J'Accuse收到一条消息
message it's gone right and there's a
消息说对了，有一个
lot more sort of guarantees and
还有更多的保证和
acknowledgement and transactionality and
认可和交易能力以及
things like that built into those built
诸如此类的东西
into that that kind of exchange so for
进行这种交换
super high volume use cases like a kind
像这样的超大容量用例
of an event firehose you know rather
你知道的一个事件firehose
caca is great um it for a lot of the
可卡很棒，很多
other enterprise sort of garden-variety
其他企业种类的花园
enterprise use cases you're going to
您将要使用的企业用例
probably find that RabbitMQ is is mature
可能发现RabbitMQ已经成熟
enough for you and it's covered in
对你来说足够了
Gatsby has what you need um they're
盖茨比有你需要的东西
pretty complementary in a lot of ways
在很多方面都非常互补
because I think what what scoff has
因为我觉得什么sc之以鼻
strengths they are are not rabbit
他们不是兔子的长处
strengths and a lot of rabbit strings
长处和很多兔子弦
are not kafka strength either so I
也不是卡夫卡人，所以我
actually see them is really quite
真的看到他们真的很
complimentary I think is you need to pay
免费，我认为您需要付款
attention to what's your use case and
注意您的用例，以及
answer it from from that perspective but
从那个角度回答
there's a great blog entry on pivotal do
关于枢轴的事有很棒的博客文章
from Fred and mellow about this exact
来自弗雷德和醇厚的关于这个确切
thing about some of the use cases that
关于一些用例的事情
each message broker is core competencies
每个消息经纪人都是核心能力
so if you do a search for Fred mellow
因此，如果您搜索Fred mellow
rabbit Kafka on the pickle site you'll
泡菜现场的兔子卡夫卡
you'll find that article right away and
您会立即找到该文章，
you can get some additional detail but I
你可以得到一些额外的细节，但我
just kind of summarized it for you as
只是为您总结了一下
best as I could
尽我所能
ah great one or two another question on
嗯，另一个伟大的一两个问题
Kafka was is there a cockpit server
卡夫卡在那里有一个驾驶舱服务器
embedded for spring Kafka and the answer
嵌入春季卡夫卡和答案
that is yes but it's a development
是的，但这是发展
version so you don't really want to use
版本，因此您真的不想使用
that for production another question
用于生产的另一个问题
was on the spring caucus support
在春季核心小组会议上
available to apps that are not using
适用于未使用的应用
boots yes they are but it's just your
靴子是的，但那只是你的
manually you know you don't get the
手动，你知道你没有
benefit of the auto configuration and
自动配置的好处是
all the other stuff you're sort of
所有其他的东西
manually doing it yourself so you
自己手动进行操作，这样您
certainly can if you're just using rod
如果您只是使用杆当然可以
spring framework and not spring boot you
Spring Framework 而不是Spring Boot你
can definitely still pick that ah let's
绝对可以选择啊，让我们
see um to do um bunch of other questions
看到um做um其他问题
oh I think I answered this already but
哦，我想我已经回答了，但是
there was a question of what version of
有一个问题是什么版本的
PCF elastic runtime do I need to support
我需要支持PCF弹性运行时吗
the actuator integration I think we
执行器集成我认为我们
addressed that but it was spring boot
解决了这个问题，但那是 spring boot
1/5 and pivotal hundred 1.9 or up okay
1/5和关键百1.9或更高
someone else asked if we had already
有人问我们是否已经
covered micro service creation and how
涵盖了微服务创建以及如何
to deploy I know we did not and that was
部署我知道我们没有，那是
sort of outside of the scope of this
超出了此范围
webinar if you aren't interested in that
网络研讨会，如果您对此不感兴趣
there are some awesome videos that cover
有一些很棒的视频
exactly that topic one of my personal
正是我个人的那个话题
favorites I would recommend is Josh
我推荐的最爱是乔什
Long's cloud native Java if you go to
Long的云原生Java（如果您要访问）
the spring YouTube channel and there's a
春天的YouTube频道，还有一个
link for that right on the screen in
在屏幕上右侧的链接
front of you spring that IO swatch video
IO样例视频在您的眼前
you'll find the you'll you'll talk about
你会发现你会谈论
you'll find some videos from Josh long
您会发现Josh long的一些视频
on cloud native Java that covers exactly
在云原生Java上
that time another question on the app
那时应用上的另一个问题
manager in pivotal Cloud Foundry is the
关键Cloud Foundry的经理是
app manager an open source application
应用程序管理器是一个开源应用程序
that I can stall and the answer is no
我可以拖延，答案是否定的
that is something that comes with Google
那是Google随附的东西
Cloud Foundry you can certainly get
您肯定可以获得的Cloud Foundry
access to it from too little web
从太少的网络访问它
services if you're not a PCF user but it
如果您不是PCF用户，则可以提供服务
is not an open source app that you could
不是您可以使用的开源应用
solve no excuse me okay looks like we're
解决不了，好吧，看起来我们像
making some good headway on I'm just
在我身上取得一些进展
going to take a quick break from one
要从一个快速休息一下
second and run back through the log and
第二，然后遍历日志并
make sure we're getting everything here
确保我们在这里得到一切
okay very good
很好很好
all right um we are going to run out of
好吧，我们要用光了
time in just about it literally about a
时间差不多就是一个
minute and a half so unfortunately I
一分半钟，我很不幸
think I'm going to have to I I really
认为我真的要去II
want to continue to answer all these
想继续回答所有这些
questions but literally the system is
问题，但实际上系统是
going to cut us off in three minutes so
要在三分钟之内切断我们
rather than having extraordinarily
而不是特别
abrupt end to the webinar on will I'm
我即将结束网络研讨会
going to log out I think we can can save
要注销我认为我们可以保存
your questions
你的问题
and of the ones that I'm not able to
和那些我无法
answer if you want to try to hit me up
如果您想尝试打我，请回答
on Twitter um I am I'm easily findable
在Twitter上，我很容易找到
at Peter Humphrey or you can just hit
在彼得·汉弗莱（Peter Humphrey）或您可以
spring central and we'll try to address
Spring Central，我们将尝试解决
your question I'll try to address your
您的问题，我将尽力解决您的问题
question there um maybe maybe follow me
问题在那里，也许也许跟着我
on Twitter or something and we can we
在Twitter之类的网站上，我们可以
can pick up in the meantime on now would
可以在此期间回升
be a great time in the last few seconds
在最后几秒钟过得很开心
we have here just to check out those
我们在这里只是检查那些
attachments and links um and definitely
附件和链接um，而且绝对是
try out the public beta of spring cloud
试用Spring Cloud的公开测试版
services on the container networking for
容器网络上的服务
cloud foundry that's pretty hot and then
云铸造厂很热，然后
uh you know if you're a user of both
呃，你知道你是否是两者的用户
technologies please by all means sign up
请务必注册技术
for the United experienced team
为美联航经验丰富的团队
interview we'll make sure that that link
采访中，我们将确保该链接
is back up and working in just a couple
备份并仅需几个工作
minutes here so maybe check back a
分钟在这里，所以也许回来看看
little bit later today and even more
今天晚一点甚至更多
than welcome to sign up if you have any
如果有的话欢迎注册
questions on that please feel free to
关于这个问题，请随时
hit me on Twitter at Peter Humphrey
在Peter Humphrey的Twitter上打我
Rhett's pretty central on and I think
Rhett非常重要，我认为
that's all we have time for today I
这就是我们今天的时间
really appreciate the questions I'm
非常感谢我的问题
sorry we couldn't get to all of them we
抱歉，我们无法解决所有问题
just have too many but um and look
只是有太多，但嗯，看看
forward to seeing you on another webinar
期待在另一个网络研讨会上见到您
very soon this week this is being
这周很快
recorded and the slides and replay will
记录下来，幻灯片和重放将
be published to the pivotal website and
被发布到关键网站并
the bright hot channel so if you want to
明亮的热门频道，所以如果您想
share those with your colleagues they're
与您的同事分享
certainly available for you
当然适合你
and we encourage you to come back and
我们鼓励您回来，
check the Tivoli oh and spring spring
检查Tivoli哦和spring spring
tie-dye our website for future webinars
扎染我们的网站，以备将来举行网络研讨会
we're really ramping up on the webinar
我们真的在网络研讨会上
program all across the company so
在整个公司范围内进行编程
there's a lot of kinds of cool stuff
有很多很酷的东西
happening every month great okay a
每个月都会发生，好吧
mother is anything you want stay tuned i
妈妈是你想要保持关注的任何东西
know i'm just thank you everyone for
知道我只是感谢大家
attending this webinar and if you have
参加此网络研讨会，如果您有
any follow-up questions you can follow
您可以关注的任何后续问题
me on twitter and ask me over there i
我在推特上问我
twitter handle is it my job of a 23 I
推特手柄是我23岁时的工作
believe it's at the beginning of the
相信这是在开始的时候
slide deck so you can get it from there
滑轨，因此您可以从那里得到它
thanks
谢谢
you
您